http://www.nufern.com/privacy

Coherent Privacy Notice
This privacy policy explains what information may be collected during your visit to our website, when you have any other business contact with us and how we use this information. In addition, you will learn more about your rights.
Responsible for this website and the processing of personal data according to this privacy policy is Coherent Inc, 5100 Patrick Henry Drive, Santa Clara, CA 95054 USA (“Coherent Inc.”, “we” or “us”). Further contact details can be found in our imprint.
Coherent, Inc. processes the personal data in the USA. To ensure an adequate level of data protection for citizens of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or Switzerland, processing is based on the Privacy Shield. You can view the certification of Coherent here: https://www.privacyshield.gov/list.
1. Visiting our website
When you visit our website, we collect the following information, from your browser:
the IP address of your computer
date and time of access
name and address of the requested file
transferred data volume
report whether the retrieval was successful
identification data of the browser and operating system used
the name of your internet service provider
This data is processed in order to technically facilitate the use of the website. We use browsing data of our users for creating aggregated statistics (so that statistics do not show data about a single user but only about the collected data of a number of users), to learn what is of interest to users in order to improve our websites and offering. We also use the browsing data for maintaining or restoring the security of our offer or to detect and correct technical defects and errors.
2. Contact (contact form and newsletter)
If you provide us with personal data via the contact form or by e-mail, this data will be used for the purpose of answering your inquiry or to give you access to the services you have requested (for example to provide information via our newsletter). If your request is directed to another Coherent company, we will forward it to that company.
3. Contractual and marketing purposes
Coherent uses personal data about business partners and customers to provide information and services to customers and business partners. Coherent specifically uses personal information to help customers and business partners to complete a transaction or order, to enable communication and collaboration, to deliver products/services, to invoice for purchased products/services, and to provide ongoing service or support.
We also use personal information for reporting purposes, such as ensuring a high level of customer service, assessing the quality of products and services, for manufacturing processes and quality control, to manage electronic signatures, to simplify internal management processes, to maintain, manage and comply with legal, regulatory, compliance and auditing obligations, policies and procedures, for operational continuity and/or disaster recovery procedures, to access sales or order portals or select services.
We may also occasionally use personal information to contact customers and business partners and to conduct surveys for marketing and quality assurance purposes. You have the right to object to this use.
4. Cookies
When you visit our website, you will be asked whether you want to activate so-called “cookies” (text files that are stored on your computer). Cookies allow us, for example, to adapt our website to your interests or to save your password.
If you agree to the use of cookies and answer the question with “yes”, we store information in the form of a cookie on your computer, which helps us to automatically recognize your computer on your next visit.
If you do not want us to recognize your computer, answer the question about the activation of cookies with “no”. You can also set your Internet browser to delete cookies from your hard drive, block all cookies or to warn you before a cookie is stored.
Detailed information on the cookies used and configuration options can be found in our cookie guidelines.
5. Retention of personal data
We only store personal data for as long as it is necessary for the provision of the services requested by you or for the purpose of processing your data.
Data that cannot be connected to an individual can be stored permanently.
6. Sharing personal data
If you wish to contact another Coherent company via our contact forms, we will forward your request to them and the receiving Coherent company will process your data for these purposes and stores them for as long as required for the provision of services or possible future business contacts. We collaborate with providers who support us in providing our services, performances and the offer on this website. These service providers (agents) process data on our behalf and under our control and for the purposes described in this data protection declaration. In addition, we may disclose personal data to suppliers and cooperation partners in accordance with the principles of Privacy Shield where necessary for the provision of services.
We may be required by U.S. law to disclose personal information to U.S. authorities. In these cases, we limit the publication to the extent that is legally mandatory.
We may also disclose personal information to the holders of such rights, advisers and authorities to enforce our rights or to protect our rights or the rights of third parties.
7. Special information for persons from the European Economic Area (EEA) or Switzerland
If you live in the European Economic Area, in Switzerland or Coherent is subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulation, you have certain rights, about which we would like to inform you about:
a) General rights
You can request information about the data stored about your person.
Furthermore, in justified cases you can also request the deletion, correction or restriction of the processing of your data and object to the processing of your data.
b) Revocation of your consent
If you have consented to the processing of your personal data on the website, you can revoke this consent at any time with effect for the future.
c) Choice
If personal information covered by this Privacy Policy is used for a new purpose that is materially different from that for which the personal information was originally collected
or subsequently authorized, or if it is to be disclosed to a third party who is not an agent, we provide you the the opportunity to choose whether to use or disclose the personal data.
With regard to sensitive personal data, we offer individuals the opportunity to explicitly consent (“opt-in”) to the disclosure of their data to non-authorized third parties or to the use of their personal data for purposes other than those originally intended or later permitted by the individuals.
d) contact and exercise of rights; supervision
To exercise these rights or if you have any questions or comments, please contact us directly in writing or by e-mail:
Mark Rakic, Data Protection Officer
privacy@Coherent.com
Data Protection Officer, c/o Coherent, Inc.
5100 Patrick Henry Drive
Santa Clara, CA 95054, USA
If you are a citizen of an EEA Member State, you can contact the Data Protection Panel in the event of unresolved complaints:
http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm
As a Swiss citizen, you can contact the Federal Data Protection Commissioner at the following address if you have any unresolved complaints:
https://www.edoeb.admin.ch
Should Coherent or the Data Protection Panel/Federal Data Protection Officer determine that Coherent has not complied with this information, Coherent will take reasonable steps to counteract adverse effects and promote future compliance.
Coherent and its U.S.-based partners are also subject to the investigative and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission, the regulatory authority responsible for the Privacy Shield.
866-466-0214
7 Airport Park Road, East Granby, CT 06026
© 2016 Nufern. All rights reserved.
Use of this website signifies your agreement to the Terms of Use.
Terms and Conditions
Privacy
Feedback
Sitemap
Shopping Cart - 0 items ($0.00)
Request a Quote -
0 items
CART (0)
